Contact

shrawanshaky3@gmail.com 9860209696 (Mobile) shrawanshaky3@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shrawan-shakya-827550194 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Mobile Application Development
Web Development
Game Development

Shrawan shakya

Developer at Woppri Gaming Bāgmatī

Summary

I have worked in past few projects for Android app development and Web development. I have done my final year thesis project on Game development. Currently, I am in my final year of Bachelor's degree BSc(Hons) in Computing at Softwarica college of IT and E-Commerce. At present, I am working as full stack developer on Woppri Gaming projects for web and mobile app development.

Experience

Woppri Gaming
Full Stack Developer
October 2020 - Present (5 months)
Bāgmatī, Nepal

GoodLuck Consult Pvt Ltd Associate Photo Editor June 2018 - January 2019 (8 months) New Road, Kathmandu

Photoshop experience

Artistic ability

Creativity

Manage workload

Hotel Metropolitan Kantipur Receptionist March 2016 - February 2017 (1 year)

Paknajol, Kathmandu

Multitasking capabilities

Organizational abilities

Effective communication skills

Technical skills

Education

Coventry University

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology · (2016 - 2020)

NCC Education

High School Diploma, Information Technology · (2017 - 2019)